<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Generated on Thu, 16 May 2019 05:35:02 -0700 -->
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://steamcommunity.com/games/252950" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <title>Rocket League RSS Feed</title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://steamcommunity.com/games/252950]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[Events and Announcements for Rocket League]]></description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <generator>Steam Community RSS</generator>
    <image>
      <url>https://steamcdn-a.akamaihd.net/steamcommunity/public/images/apps/252950/e17b7226bd3d24d9af279c3b8408c6c0d2df7406.jpg</url>
      <title>Rocket League</title>
      <link>https://steamcommunity.com/games/252950</link>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Rocket League's Summer 2019 Roadmap</title>
      <description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/iygScY5.jpg&quot; &gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's hard to believe that we're almost to the halfway mark of 2019, but believe it you should, because it means that we're ready for a brand new Roadmap that sheds some light on the new features and improvements we're bringing to the game over the next several months.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Of course, you've probably already read this month's &amp;quot;&lt;a class=&quot;bb_link&quot; href=&quot;https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?url=https://www.rocketleague.com/news/psyonix-is-joining-the-epic-family-/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noreferrer&quot; &gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Epic News&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;bb_link_host&quot;&gt;[www.rocketleague.com]&lt;/span&gt;,&amp;quot; which is why we also want to assure you (and the rest of our community) that &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Rocket League&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; will continue to be shaped by the same development team that it always has even if our family is getting quite a bit bigger. The game will also continue to be fueled and inspired by the passion and feedback of our dedicated playerbase just as it was before.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;With that in mind, let's take a closer look at what you can expect to see in the next few months of 2019!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;bb_h1&quot;&gt;Summer Event with Limited-Time Events&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;Next month, we will kick off the biggest in-game event that &lt;i&gt;Rocket League&lt;/i&gt; has ever had, featuring several limited-time events. While the event on the whole will share the same in-game currency for items that can be redeemed inside the event store, the items found in the event store itself will change as we move through different points in the promotion; giving you more in-game items to earn than ever before.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We know that players can sometimes earn more event currency than they sometimes use, so we're addressing that by adding XP Level-Up Packs in the event store as well (a &lt;i&gt;Rocket League&lt;/i&gt; first)! That means that players will be able to redeem event currency for XP Level-Up Packs that grant 10 Tier Points for Rocket Pass -- allowing you to boost your Rocket Pass Tiers in a super-fast and super-convenient way!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;bb_h1&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Party-Up System, Inventory Management, and Trading&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;The community has been asking us for quicker ways to party-up with strangers following a good match. That functionality will be coming later this year. Soon, you'll be able to easily party-up with teammates from the post-game screen.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inventories are growing too, and that calls for better ways to organize all of your in-game items. We're happy to say that additional inventory management tools will also be added via a future update.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Finally, one of our long-term goals for 2019 and beyond is to make a number of under-the-hood, quality-of-life updates to our trading system. We’ll have more to share on that later this year.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;bb_h1&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;RLCS Season 7 World Championship Incoming!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;The &lt;b&gt;RLCS Season 7 World Championship&lt;/b&gt; at the Prudential Center in Newark, NJ is just around the corner and tickets are selling fast. &lt;a class=&quot;bb_link&quot; href=&quot;https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?url=http://tickets.rlesports.gg&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noreferrer&quot; &gt;&lt;b&gt;Get your tickets&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;bb_link_host&quot;&gt;[tickets.rlesports.gg]&lt;/span&gt; now to catch all the live action from the world's best &lt;i&gt;Rocket League&lt;/i&gt; teams. Also, Competitive Season 10 ends on Monday, May 13, so make sure you fulfill your Season Reward Level wins at your rank to earn the appropriate goodies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stay tuned next month for the full reveal of our upcoming event. Plus, you can expect to see the aforementioned features (and more) later this year. For fans looking to find out more regarding what our acquisition by Epic Games means for &lt;i&gt;Rocket League&lt;/i&gt; and Psyonix in the long-term -- there's nothing new to report just yet, but we'll keep you informed as soon as we have an update.</description>
      <link><![CDATA[https://steamcommunity.com/games/252950/announcements/detail/1625148260772549686]]></link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 17:36:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Dirkened</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://steamcommunity.com/games/252950/announcements/detail/1625148260772549686</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Community Spotlight: JZR</title>
      <description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/z0IZSFM.jpg&quot; &gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Big things have humble beginnings. Learning to pull the most insane aerial backboard double touches starts out by just trying to strike a slow-moving ball with all four wheels firmly planted on the ground. Becoming one of the biggest content creators in the &lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rocket League&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt; community—someone who produces &lt;a class=&quot;bb_link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=huGwduwVvJ8&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noreferrer&quot; &gt;&lt;b&gt;seemingly impossible freestyle goals&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;—can start as a quick upload of someone practicing freekicks in soccer. That's Joni &amp;quot;JHZER&amp;quot; Humaloja (now simply known as &amp;quot;JZR&amp;quot;). Before he was pushing the limits of what was possible on the virtual pitch, this is precisely how the aerial extraordinaire started his YouTube career.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;His very first upload was a simple, &lt;a class=&quot;bb_link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7I54LIZV_ag&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noreferrer&quot; &gt;&lt;b&gt;single-cam video&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; of him practicing his soccer skills in his hometown of Nummela, Finland. Like so many who have turned &lt;i&gt;Rocket League&lt;/i&gt; skills into a career, JZR's love for soccer proved to be the gateway to the video game. Before JZR was showing his viewers how to be one of the best players in a &lt;i&gt;Rocket League&lt;/i&gt; lobby, he started by learning the basics of &lt;i&gt;Supersonic Acrobatic Rocket Powered Battle Cars&lt;/i&gt; (&lt;i&gt;SARPBC&lt;/i&gt;)&lt;i&gt;. &lt;/i&gt;This turned out to be the first game JZR started taking seriously.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;I started playing &lt;i&gt;SARPBC &lt;/i&gt;seriously pretty much from the beginning,&amp;quot; JZR said. &amp;quot;I loved the game because it was really similar to real-life sports. You're in total control of the car. &lt;i&gt;SARPBC &lt;/i&gt;gave players the car, boost, and the ball. From there, it’s all about what you can do with them. It's the best feeling when you realize how you struggled with something last time you played and now you are more comfortable with it. You feel proud and want to improve on the next thing.&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/w7vdUIM.jpg&quot; &gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;That improvement would eventually lead to the creation of content including some of the most insane &lt;i&gt;Rocket League&lt;/i&gt; goals on YouTube. Before &lt;a class=&quot;bb_link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/jhzer/featured&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noreferrer&quot; &gt;&lt;b&gt;his YouTube channel&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; got fully off the ground, JZR wasn't sure if YouTube would be his career path, despite it being his dream. Even though soccer was his first YouTube upload and the beginning of his love for competition, he decided to hang up the cleats after playing for 9 years to focus on his college. At that time, the goal was to go from college to university to study nanoscience (university comes after college in Finland). Even while juggling higher education, college brought free time, and free time began to fill with &lt;i&gt;SARPBC&lt;/i&gt;. But, he wasn't able to drop everything and embrace SARPBC just yet.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;After college, it was time to complete his military service—a government mandate for all men over 18 years old in Finland. JZR, who served as a Navy Scout, describes it as one of the toughest times of his life, but credits his service for teaching him discipline and respect.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Following military service, JZR found himself at a crossroads. He was back at university, but his passion for &lt;i&gt;SARPBC &lt;/i&gt;still lingered. Creating videos on a regular basis for a YouTube channel is no easy task by itself. JZR taught himself to edit his videos, and had to learn new techniques as he went along. Throw in a university course load studying nanoscience in chemistry, and you have a recipe to get stretched pretty thin. That's when he had to make the decision between the traditional path versus the unconventional.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;I'm still in university, but I've taken time off for a year now to focus on content creating. That's where my real dreams are,&amp;quot; he said. Having the support of loved ones always helps, and JZR says he has that too. &amp;quot;My family is super supportive and always encourages me to do what I really want to do in life. They knew how much I enjoyed gaming already and that I did videos before this for a long time. So, they were just proud and happy for the success of the channel.&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now, being laser-focused on &lt;i&gt;Rocket League&lt;/i&gt; and content creation, JZR is all about elevating his game, both on the pitch and on his channel. He came on the scene with crazy mechanics known as &amp;quot;freestyling.&amp;quot; Freestyling is when players go for goals in the flashiest way possible. He and his partner on the pitch, MK, are practically &lt;i&gt;Rocket League&lt;/i&gt; magicians, setting up ridiculous passing plays to one another all while spinning multiple times in midair with ease. JZR and MK's partnership goes way back to three years ago when they were part of a freestyling team called Nixus.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;From the first game we played together I saw how good he was at passing. We had amazing chemistry. We've been playing ever since and haven't stopped. Nowadays, he is one of my best friends. I've met him several times in real life and I'm truly happy that he's part of my life.&amp;quot; JZR admits that while his channel, and his playstyle with MK, started out with a focus on freestyling, he's been trying to distance himself from being labeled a &amp;quot;freestyler.&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;I started freestyling on &lt;i&gt;SARPBC &lt;/i&gt;in 2011. I thought it would be cool to score goals while spinning like crazy in air for montages, because people really didn’t do them back then. My viewers liked the goals, so coming up with different tricks became my thing. Nowadays in &lt;i&gt;Rocket League&lt;/i&gt;, my passion is more in competitive, so I haven’t been a freestyler in a long time. I don’t come up with new tricks anymore on purpose. It’s more like crazy stuff just happens when I’m trying my best but also improvising on the go.&amp;quot; JZR still likes to follow the freestyling scene and particularly enjoys the goals of other content creators like MuiricleS.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/pgFbaxi.jpg&quot; &gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When not producing videos, JZR has dabbled in &lt;i&gt;Rocket League's&lt;/i&gt; competitive landscape. He was part of the now defunct FlipSid3 Tactics in 2017, and is looking to refuel that competitive fire. He recently competed in the EU Play-In stage of the &lt;b&gt;Rival Series&lt;/b&gt; this season. &amp;quot;After a long time not competing I have started to focus on that again, and I'm improving myself as a player,&amp;quot; JZR said. &amp;quot;I’m doing competitive highlights more than freestyling, so making those highlight videos and competing is easier.&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether it's competing, practicing, or creating content for a YouTube channel, playing that much &lt;i&gt;Rocket League&lt;/i&gt; can lead to burnout. JZR's got that covered, too. He tries to take time to himself away from screens when he can, or play something other than Rocket League to give himself a break. &amp;quot;In my spare time, I try to take care of myself as well as I can,&amp;quot; he said. &amp;quot;Workout out at the gym and running are my favorite ways to do that, and I'm still playing soccer for fun.&amp;quot; He enjoys playing other games with his teammate MK like &lt;i&gt;Dead by Daylight&lt;/i&gt;, &lt;i&gt;Tekken&lt;/i&gt;, &lt;i&gt;CounterStrike: Global Offensive&lt;/i&gt;, &lt;i&gt;Call of Duty&lt;/i&gt;, and &lt;i&gt;Overwatch&lt;/i&gt;, just to name a few.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even with all the games he plays for fun, &lt;i&gt;Rocket League&lt;/i&gt; is still JZR's mainstay. He always goes back to it to improve his skills, pushing the boundaries of what's possible, and helping others elevate their game with tutorial videos on how to get to those top competitive ranks. &amp;quot;I still get super hyped about good goals even though I've been playing&lt;i&gt; Rocket League&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;SARPBC&lt;/i&gt; for almost 10 years. That just shows that goals just keep getting better, and that thought makes me happy.&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Check out &lt;a class=&quot;bb_link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/jhzer/featured&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noreferrer&quot; &gt;&lt;b&gt;JZR's YouTube channel&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and follow him on &lt;a class=&quot;bb_link&quot; href=&quot;https://twitter.com/jhzer&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noreferrer&quot; &gt;&lt;b&gt;Twitter&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to see his latest highlights and tutorials.</description>
      <link><![CDATA[https://steamcommunity.com/games/252950/announcements/detail/1624021722886278260]]></link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 17:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Dirkened</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://steamcommunity.com/games/252950/announcements/detail/1624021722886278260</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch Notes v1.62</title>
      <description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/9N9cHCt.jpg&quot; &gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Scheduled Release: April 30, 2019, 10:00 a.m. PDT / 5:00 p.m. UTC (All Platforms)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;bb_h1&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;CHANGES AND UPDATES&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;b&gt;Audio&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;Echo effect on ball effect has been adjusted&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reduced dynamic range of game audio based on community reception and feedback&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;bb_h1&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;b&gt;General&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adjusted volume of fireworks on Champions Field (all variants)&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed the diagonal kickoff position on Champions Field&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;An appropriate Club Tag worn by multiple players in a match should no longer be filtered on only one of those players&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Resolved increase of ‘Error 71’ matchmaking errors when trying to find an Online Match&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Player Banners previewed on Crate and Rocket Pass menus will no longer incorrectly attach to your profile&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adjusted the Paint Finish on the ‘DeLorean Time Machine’&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Friends List notifications will now appear while viewing Replays&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;bb_h1&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;KNOWN ISSUES&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;Players may see an “XP not received” message despite earning enough points&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Audio may drop out during a match for some players&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Some players may see overlapping item-loading icons when starting the game after receiving a large number of new Customization Items&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;(Rumble) Some players may not be able to pick up boost after being hit with the Disruptor power-up&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Crates received while playing may not stack with Crates in inventory, but they will stack correctly after a game restart&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <link><![CDATA[https://steamcommunity.com/games/252950/announcements/detail/1652168586331976384]]></link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 16:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Dirkened</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://steamcommunity.com/games/252950/announcements/detail/1652168586331976384</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rocket Pass 3 with Challenges Live Now</title>
      <description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/husUrPh.jpg&quot; &gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rocket Pass 3 is live and gives players faster ways to Tier-Up with new Weekly Challenges.  The Challenges for Week 2 are now live! Get three new Challenges each week throughout Rocket Pass 3, or upgrade to Rocket Pass Premium and get a total of six. With Rocket Pass Premium's initial 50% XP bonus and Weekly Challenges, you'll reach the Pro Tiers faster than ever! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How far will you go?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rocket Pass 3 will run until July 29, so jump into Online Matches to start climbing those Rocket Pass Tiers!</description>
      <link><![CDATA[https://steamcommunity.com/games/252950/announcements/detail/1652168586297839319]]></link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 18:07:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Dirkened</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://steamcommunity.com/games/252950/announcements/detail/1652168586297839319</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Competitive Season 10 Rewards Revealed</title>
      <description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/hVnK0UC.jpg&quot; &gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rocket League's&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt; tenth Competitive Season will come to a close next month. That means it's time to reveal the upcoming Season Rewards. We're excited to announce that the rewards for Competitive Season 10 will be brand new Goal Explosions!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Competitive Season 10 will end, and Season 11 will begin, on May 13. Like previous Competitive Seasons, there will be unique reward for ranks Bronze, Silver, Gold, Platinum, Diamond, Champion, and Grand Champion. The Grand Champion Rank will have its own unique reward in addition to the the Season 10 Grand Champion Title.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Check out the video below to see the new Goal Explosions in action.&lt;br&gt;  &lt;br&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;bb_link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VcR4wTACyNc&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noreferrer&quot;  id=&quot;dynamiclink_0&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VcR4wTACyNc&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In addition to the unique Grand Champion Rewards and Titles, Extra Mode Grand Champion Titles are returning for Season 10. Extra Mode Titles for the Grand Champion Rank debuted in Season 9 and will be back this season. See the full distribution breakdown below:&lt;br&gt;  &lt;br&gt;COMPETITIVE AND EXTRA MODE REWARDS&lt;br&gt;  &lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      &lt;b&gt;Bronze I or higher&lt;/b&gt; – Season 10 – Bronze Goal Explosion&lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      &lt;b&gt;Silver I or higher&lt;/b&gt; – Season 10 – Silver Goal Explosion + lower Goal Explosions&lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      &lt;b&gt;Gold I or higher&lt;/b&gt; – Season 10 – Gold Goal Explosion + lower Goal Explosions&lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      &lt;b&gt;Platinum I or higher&lt;/b&gt; – Season 10 – Platinum Goal Explosion + lower Goal Explosions&lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      &lt;b&gt;Diamond I or higher&lt;/b&gt; – Season 10 – Diamond Goal Explosion + lower Goal Explosions&lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      &lt;b&gt;Champion I or higher&lt;/b&gt; – Season 10 – Champion Goal Explosion + lower Goal Explosions&lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;br&gt;GRAND CHAMPION REWARDS&lt;br&gt;  &lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      &lt;b&gt;Competitive Grand Champion&lt;/b&gt; – ‘Season 10 – Grand Champion’ In-Game Title + Grand Champion Goal Explosion + all Season 10 Goal Explosions&lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      &lt;b&gt;Rumble Grand Champion&lt;/b&gt; – ‘Season 10 – RNG Champ’ In-Game Title + Grand Champion Goal Explosion + all Season 10 Goal Explosions&lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      &lt;b&gt;Dropshot Grand Champion&lt;/b&gt; – ‘Season 10 – Floor Destroyer’ In-Game Title + Grand Champion Goal Explosion + all Season 10 Goal Explosions&lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      &lt;b&gt;Hoops Grand Champion&lt;/b&gt; – ‘Season 10 – Dunk Master’ In-Game Title + Grand Champion Goal Explosion + all Season 10 Goal Explosions&lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      &lt;b&gt;Snow Day Grand Champion &lt;/b&gt;– ‘Season 10 – Blizzard Wizard’ In-Game Title + Grand Champion Goal Explosion + all Season 10 Goal Explosions&lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;u&gt;(Note: Grand Champion In-Game Titles for Extra Modes are earned by achieving Grand Champion Rank in each individual Extra Mode)&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;  &lt;br&gt;You still have a few more weeks left in Season 10 to hit your goals. Remember, you have to complete your placement matches in a Competitive Playlist and fulfill the appropriate Season Reward Level in order to earn your rewards for Competitive Season 10. Competitive Season 11 will have the same soft reset that previous competitive seasons have had. You will need to complete 10 placement matches per Competitive Playlist to earn your rank, which will likely be near your previously held rank.&lt;br&gt;  &lt;br&gt;If you're still working on reaching that next rank, be sure to bring your A-game to get those wins before May 13 when Season 10 ends and Season 11, begins. As always, good luck and have fun!</description>
      <link><![CDATA[https://steamcommunity.com/games/252950/announcements/detail/1652168586297513316]]></link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 17:12:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Dirkened</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://steamcommunity.com/games/252950/announcements/detail/1652168586297513316</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shazam Items Soar Into Rocket League</title>
      <description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/8THeU85.jpg&quot; &gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHAZAM! Starting right now, you can unlock new in-game items inspired by the hit DC Comics film, and the best part is, they're free!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just as Billy Batson says, &amp;quot;Shazam!,&amp;quot; to get his super powers, so too will you get your items! Just enter key word &amp;quot;shazam&amp;quot; in the &amp;quot;Redeem Code&amp;quot; menu to get the official Shazam Octane Decal and Shazam Wheels. These items may not come with super strength or bullet immunity, but you'll still look super cool when your Battle-Car goes flying through the air!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Check out &lt;u&gt;Shazam! &lt;/u&gt;in theaters now.</description>
      <link><![CDATA[https://steamcommunity.com/games/252950/announcements/detail/1654419750122212491]]></link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 17:10:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Dirkened</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://steamcommunity.com/games/252950/announcements/detail/1654419750122212491</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch Notes v1.61 [Esports Shop Update]</title>
      <description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/KQ9kKqC.jpg&quot; &gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Scheduled Release: April 16, 2019, 10:00 a.m. PDT / 5:00 p.m. UTC (All Platforms)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;bb_h1&quot;&gt;THE HEADLINES&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;  &lt;li&gt;    New Customization Items are now available via Esports Shop&lt;br&gt;  &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;    Replay FX: You can now create and edit screenshots while viewing Replays&lt;br&gt;  &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;    HDR support has been added to PS4, PS4 Pro, and Xbox One S&lt;br&gt;  &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;bb_h1&quot;&gt;NEW CONTENT&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rocket Pass 3&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;  &lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      Rocket Pass 3 begins on April 17 at 10 AM a.m. PDT / 5 p.m. UTC&lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;b&gt;Esports Shop&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;  &lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      Customization Items are now available via the new Esports Shop&lt;br&gt;      &lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;        &lt;li&gt;          Select ‘Shop’ from the Main Menu, then select ‘Esports Shop’&lt;br&gt;        &lt;/li&gt;      &lt;/ul&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      Items in the Esports Shop can be purchased with Esports Tokens&lt;br&gt;      &lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;        &lt;li&gt;          Esports Tokens can be purchased with your local currency, and cannot be purchased with Keys&lt;br&gt;        &lt;/li&gt;      &lt;/ul&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      Esports Store items are available in time-limited intervals&lt;br&gt;      &lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;        &lt;li&gt;          Each item will have a timer located below the preview thumbnail in the Esports Store&lt;br&gt;        &lt;/li&gt;      &lt;/ul&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;b&gt;Monstercat&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;  &lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      New Antennas are now available in the ‘Monstercat’ folder:&lt;br&gt;      &lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;        &lt;li&gt;          ‘Notaker’&lt;br&gt;        &lt;/li&gt;        &lt;li&gt;          ‘FWLR’&lt;br&gt;        &lt;/li&gt;      &lt;/ul&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/rx71OZp.jpg&quot; &gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;bb_h1&quot;&gt;CHANGES AND UPDATES&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rocket Pass Challenges&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;  &lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      Challenges are a new way to unlock Tiers in Rocket Pass and the Rocket Pass Premium Upgrade&lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      Select ‘Rocket Pass’ from the Main Menu, then select the ‘Challenges’ Tab in the upper-left corner&lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      Each Challenge is worth three, five, or eight ‘Tier Points’&lt;br&gt;      &lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;        &lt;li&gt;          Earning ten Tier Points by completing Challenges will unlock your next Rocket Pass Tier&lt;br&gt;        &lt;/li&gt;        &lt;li&gt;          Earning a new level via the progression system is worth now worth ten Tier Points&lt;br&gt;        &lt;/li&gt;      &lt;/ul&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      When Rocket Pass is active, three new Challenges are added every Wednesday at 10 AM a.m. PDT / 5 p.m. UTC&lt;br&gt;      &lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;        &lt;li&gt;          An additional three Challenges (six total) are available to players with the Premium Upgrade&lt;br&gt;        &lt;/li&gt;        &lt;li&gt;          Challenges must be completed within their week-long period&lt;br&gt;        &lt;/li&gt;        &lt;li&gt;          If you purchase the Premium Upgrade more than one week after a Rocket Pass is released, you will earn Tier Points for completed Premium Challenges, so long as their requirements were completed during their original week-long period&lt;br&gt;        &lt;/li&gt;      &lt;/ul&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/T1FQnus.jpg&quot; &gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Replay FX&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;  &lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      You can now enable Replay FX within the Replay Viewer&lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      While viewing a Replay, press the Share button (PS4), View button (Xbox) or F key (PC) to bring up the Replay FX menu&lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      The Replay FX menu has seven options, including:&lt;br&gt;      &lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;        &lt;li&gt;          Focus Distance (Controls Depth of Field Distance)&lt;br&gt;        &lt;/li&gt;        &lt;li&gt;          Focus Blur (Controls how intense DOF Blur will be)&lt;br&gt;        &lt;/li&gt;        &lt;li&gt;          Focus Strength (Controls how much DOF Kernel will affect far plane)&lt;br&gt;        &lt;/li&gt;        &lt;li&gt;          Green Screen (with Red, Green, and Blue options)&lt;br&gt;        &lt;/li&gt;        &lt;li&gt;          Image Filter (with ten filters to select from)&lt;br&gt;        &lt;/li&gt;        &lt;li&gt;          Image Filter Intensity&lt;br&gt;        &lt;/li&gt;        &lt;li&gt;          Vignette&lt;br&gt;        &lt;/li&gt;      &lt;/ul&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      Replay FX options apply to an active Replay or when paused so you can take a screenshot&lt;br&gt;      &lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;        &lt;li&gt;          Use your platform’s screenshot function once you have a shot set up with your Replay FX of choice&lt;br&gt;        &lt;/li&gt;      &lt;/ul&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;b&gt;Crates and Keys&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;  &lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      Crate drop rates can now be viewed in-game on the Crate Preview Screen&lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      Players in Belgium can no longer open Crates with Keys due to government regulations&lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      Players in the Netherlands can no longer open Crates with Keys due to government regulations&lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;General&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;  &lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      [PS4, Xbox] You can now invite players on the same platform to your party without adding them to your Friends List&lt;br&gt;      &lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;        &lt;li&gt;          Select Create a Party, then select the Search function using Square (PS4) or X (Xbox)&lt;br&gt;        &lt;/li&gt;        &lt;li&gt;          This will bring up your console’s PSN ID/Gamertag search window&lt;br&gt;        &lt;/li&gt;      &lt;/ul&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      HDR is now supported on PS4, PS4 Pro, and Xbox One S&lt;br&gt;      &lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;        &lt;li&gt;          HDR requires a compatible television/display and HDMI cable&lt;br&gt;        &lt;/li&gt;      &lt;/ul&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      [Xbox One X] Reduced default color saturation when HDR is enabled&lt;br&gt;      &lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;        &lt;li&gt;          This new default setting is present on PS4, PS4 Pro, and Xbox One S when HDR is enabled on those platforms&lt;br&gt;        &lt;/li&gt;      &lt;/ul&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      Steering and Aerial Sensitivity Controls now be adjusted in increments of 0.01 instead of 0.1&lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;bb_h1&quot;&gt;Bug Fixes&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;General&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;  &lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      Fixed an issue that delayed steering, throttle, and handbrake input by one physics frame      &lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      Jump ball now behaves correctly on Dunk House (Hoops) in Free Play      &lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      Vehicles should now respawn correctly after resetting the ball on Steam Workshop maps      &lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      In-game voice chat icon will no longer appear when voice chat is disabled      &lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      Players can now reconnect more than once if they crash or disconnect multiple times during a Ranked match      &lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      Biomass no longer removes color from trim on some Painted Car Bodies      &lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      All appropriate ‘Snowy’ maps will now appear when playing the Snow Day game mode      &lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      ‘Shots on Goal’ now correctly register as a stat when playing Hoops      &lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      Rebalanced audio on the ‘’89 Batmobile’     &lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      Fixed a bug that caused some players with very large Customization Item inventories to crash when scrolling through their Garage or Inventory      &lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      Fixed a bug causing some players to crash when leaving a Custom Training pack      &lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      All items should now display correctly when viewing in the Crate preview screen      &lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      [Switch] Fixed a bug causing the game to freeze when using a player profile not linked to a Nintendo Account      &lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      Previous Party Chat messages no longer carry over into Training, Private Matches or Online Matches&lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;br&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;bb_h1&quot;&gt;KNOWN ISSUES&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      [Switch] Depth of Field controls are disabled in Replay FX      &lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      &lt;br&gt;Players may see an “XP not received” message despite earning the required number of points     &lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      Audio may drop out during a match for some players      &lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      Friends List notifications will not appear while viewing Replays      &lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      An incorrect error message may appear if you try to change your Rocket ID if PsyNet is down      &lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      [Switch] Upon entering a match, some players may not be immediately brought to the Player View Camera      &lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      Some players may see overlapping item-loading icons when starting the game after receiving a large number of new Customization Items    &lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      [Rumble] Some players may not be able to pick up boost after being hit with the Disruptor power-up&lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;      Crates received while playing may not stack with Crates in inventory, but they will stack correctly after a game restart&lt;br&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
      <link><![CDATA[https://steamcommunity.com/games/252950/announcements/detail/3290351778414029074]]></link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 16:08:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Dirkened</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://steamcommunity.com/games/252950/announcements/detail/3290351778414029074</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rocket Pass 3 and Weekly Challenges Revealed</title>
      <description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://steamcdn-a.akamaihd.net/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/9036925/009371bdc364505c1e2d35d7f346052deec979d7.jpg&quot; &gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Rocket Pass 3 just around the corner, we wanted to let you know what to expect on April 17. Along with an entirely new line of Free and Premium items unique to this Rocket Pass, Weekly Challenges are also being added to the mix. These Challenges will allow players to Tier Up even faster. Before you eagerly take the field on day one, here is everything you need to know about Rocket Pass 3 and Weekly Challenges.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;bb_h1&quot;&gt;Are You Up To The Challenge? &lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weekly Challenges will go live on the first day of Rocket Pass 3, and will add a new way to climb Tiers. Specifically, Tiers are now gained with a new Rocket League reward system, known as &amp;quot;Tier Points.&amp;quot; Tier Points are earned by completing Challenges but they're also earned by gaining XP after Online Matches, similar to how it worked in Rocket Pass 1 and 2.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How does it work together now? Well, in Rocket Pass 3, each Tier requires 10 Tier Points to advance to the next Tier. Challenges will be worth three, five, and eight Tier Points depending on the difficulty of the Challenge. In addition to the Tier Points you gain from completing Weekly ~Challenges, you can also Tier-Up from XP as mentioned above. Every time you gain an XP level, you'll receive 10 Tier Points. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weekly Challenges must be completed during the week in which they are active. They will expire once new Challenges become active during the following week. Rocket Pass 3 will still track your progress for Premium Weekly Challenges even if you have not purchased Rocket Pass Premium, but you will only receive the Tier Points from Premium Challenges once Rocket Pass Premium has been purchased. If you purchase Rocket Pass Premium late into Rocket Pass 3, you will receive the Tier Points from completed Premium Challenges in expired weeks. However, you will not be able to complete uncompleted Challenges once they expire. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Challenge list will refresh each Wednesday at 10:00 a.m. PDT (5:00 p.m. UTC) throughout Rocket Pass 3. Check out a sneak peek at the Challenge Menu and the Weekly Challenges from Week 1 in the screenshot below.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://steamcdn-a.akamaihd.net/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/9036925/a8f3d4411cb5414b0d72b43426aef34d47d12ccc.jpg&quot; &gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;bb_h1&quot;&gt;All New Items&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rocket Pass 3 will feature 20+ items in the Free track, and 50+ additional items in the Rocket Pass Premium Track, including the all-new Guardian Battle-Car. Plus, there are Decryptors to earn on the Free track and a total of 10 Keys in Rocket Pass Premium. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pro Tiers are back! Pro Tiers (i.e. past Tier 70) will grant Painted items from Rocket Pass 3, and will have a chance of being Certified or Special Edition. As always, rewards earned from the Pro Tiers in Rocket Pass 3 are tradable. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;bb_h1&quot;&gt;Rocket Pass 3 &amp;amp; Challenges At a Glance&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you prefer bullet points, here's the TL;DR version of Rocket Pass 3 and Weekly Challenges:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt; Rocket Pass Premium for Rocket Pass 3 is the same price as previous Rocket Passes (10 Keys).&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; Rocket Pass 3 will have both Free and Premium Tiers, just like Rocket Pass 1 and 2.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; Rocket Pass 3 will have Weekly Challenges for both Free and Premium tracks. &lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; The Free track will have three Weekly Challenges and those with Rocket Pass Premium will get three additional Weekly Challenges. &lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; Challenges expire each Wednesday at 10 a.m. PDT (5:00 p.m. UTC) during Rocket Pass 3, and new challenges will become active at that time.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; Weekly Challenges must be completed within their active week. &lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; You cannot go back and complete expired challenges once their week has passed.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; If you purchase Rocket Pass Premium in a later week during the Rocket Pass 3, you will receive Tier Points for completed Challenges from previous weeks.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br&gt;For a full list of FAQs, be sure to check out the Rocket Pass 3 website. We hope you enjoy taking on the new Weekly Challenges in Rocket Pass 3. Good luck, have fun, and see you on April 17!</description>
      <link><![CDATA[https://steamcommunity.com/games/252950/announcements/detail/2560767999959501975]]></link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 16:49:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Psyonix Devin</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://steamcommunity.com/games/252950/announcements/detail/2560767999959501975</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Esports Shop Update and Rocket Pass 3 Coming This Month</title>
      <description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/6e5YrSq.jpg&quot; &gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our next update — the &lt;b&gt;Esports Shop Update&lt;/b&gt; — is just over the horizon, with a bunch of new content we're excited to bring to &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Rocket League&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; coming right along with it! Expected to go live on April 16 (pending first-party certification), this new update will not only include its namesake, the Esports Shop, but also &lt;b&gt;Rocket Pass 3&lt;/b&gt;, kicking off one day after that on April 17.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;bb_h1&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Introducing the Esports Shop&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;You'll now be able to show off your team pride for your favorite esport squads competing in &lt;b&gt;Rocket League Esports&lt;/b&gt;. The Esports Shop will open for business on April 16. Of course, there's still a lot more to share about the Esports Shop, but we'll reveal everything there is to know—including its items, look, and more next week.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;bb_h1&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rocket Pass 3 Incoming!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rocket Pass 3 will debut soon with a Challenge System! Get ready to climb your way to the Pro Tiers. Look for an in-depth look at Rocket Pass 3 and the new Challenge System very soon.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;bb_h1&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Replay FX, HDR Support, and More!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;We've added a new Replay FX system that content creators should enjoy. With this new toolset, you'll be able to give your replays the full &amp;quot;photo mode&amp;quot; treatment by changing the depth of field, altering backgrounds, adding green screen effects, color adjustment, and more post-processing effects. Please note that Replay FX is still in a beta phase, but the entire control suite will be available when the update goes live.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also coming in this update: HDR support for PS4, PS4 Pro, and Xbox One S.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Check out the quick bullet points below to see what to expect from the Esports Shop Update:&lt;br&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;Esports Shop&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rocket Pass 3 with Challenges (April 17)&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Replay FX&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;HDR Support&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Monstercat Flags&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;… and more!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;We're excited to bring this new content to Rocket League on April 16. Stay tuned to the blog next week when we'll be taking a deep dive into the Esports Shop, Rocket Pass 3, and Challenges.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
      <link><![CDATA[https://steamcommunity.com/games/252950/announcements/detail/1788400575265656467]]></link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 17:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Dirkened</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://steamcommunity.com/games/252950/announcements/detail/1788400575265656467</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Community Spotlight: Get to Pro-Level with Practice</title>
      <description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/z0IZSFM.jpg&quot; &gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pros of &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rocket League&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt; are almost ready to hit the field for Season 7 of the &lt;b&gt;Rocket League Championship Series (RLCS)&lt;/b&gt;! That means that League Play begins on April 6, but the best of the best just didn't get there overnight. If you want to learn to play like the pros, you're going to have to put in the time on the practice field.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since this is the first training pack roundup of 2019, this edition of Community Spotlight focuses on improving play no matter your rank. Some players may be working on the consistency of air dribbles, while newcomers are still working on getting off the ground. Whether you're just starting out in Bronze or climbing that ladder to Grand Champ, you'll find a Training Pack to improve your game and impress your opponents. Here are this month's Custom Training Packs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/4MYIgMv.jpg&quot; &gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_tr&quot;&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_th&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;#&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_th&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Author&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_th&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Name&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_th&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Difficulty&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_th&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Code&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_tr&quot;&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;1&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;Hinata&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;The ultimate warm-up&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;Diamond&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;FA24-B2B7-2E8E-193B&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_tr&quot;&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;2&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;Shia Laboost&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;Backboard LaBoomers&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;Champion&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;6501-3E56-56A4-6426&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_tr&quot;&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;3&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;Oneill&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;Groundwork Attack&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;Champion&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;3CF1-6A0E-D4B9-8B38&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_tr&quot;&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;4&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;Gweep&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;REDIRECT 10 PACK&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;Champion&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;F2A4-8700-AC81-19B2&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_tr&quot;&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;5&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;JustPlay&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;tough angles&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;Diamond&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;76C2-C5E5-100E-8847&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_tr&quot;&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;6&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;Awesup1&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;Power Shot Training&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;Platinum&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;36AE-90A0-5489-7EB5&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_tr&quot;&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;7&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;King&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;Backwards Saves&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;Platinum&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;EABD-7F2F-D4FA-46B2&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_tr&quot;&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;8&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;Floating Mongoose&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;Simple wall shots&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;Silver&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;276F-25E2-754D-D8E3&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_tr&quot;&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;9&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;Syntax&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;Upper 90 Striker Training&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;Platinum&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;div class=&quot;bb_table_td&quot;&gt;BCAC-7526-0941-D593&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;Think you've created the next great Custom Training Pack? Let us know by sharing it on &lt;a class=&quot;bb_link&quot; href=&quot;https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?url=http://discord.gg/RocketLeague&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noreferrer&quot; &gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Discord&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;bb_link_host&quot;&gt;[discord.gg]&lt;/span&gt;, &lt;a class=&quot;bb_link&quot; href=&quot;https://reddit.com/r/RocketLeague/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noreferrer&quot; &gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Reddit&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a class=&quot;bb_link&quot; href=&quot;http://twitter.com/RocketLeague&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noreferrer&quot; &gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Twitter&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. We go through fan-submitted Training Packs each month, and could even choose yours in our next Community Spotlight!&lt;br&gt;</description>
      <link><![CDATA[https://steamcommunity.com/games/252950/announcements/detail/1744489844918951757]]></link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 18:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Dirkened</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://steamcommunity.com/games/252950/announcements/detail/1744489844918951757</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>